[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "What is happening right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "happening", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["four days ago"]}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "What is going on with the East Coast weather?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "going", "on", "with", "the", "East", "Coast", "weather", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Just four days ago we were talking about wind chills.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "four", "days", "ago", "we", "were", "talking", "about", "wind", "chills", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["East Coast"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["spring"]}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Is this as extraordinary as it seems to me, Amy, or not?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "as", "extraordinary", "as", "it", "seems", "to", "me", ",", "Amy", ",", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Well, of course we've got these major extremes and the transition during spring typically produces this type of extreme weather.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "of", "course", "we", "'ve", "got", "these", "major", "extremes", "and", "the", "transition", "during", "spring", "typically", "produces", "this", "type", "of", "extreme", "weather", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hurricane Center"]}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD", "TO", "CD", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "JJ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Chad, are we heading towards a particularly extreme summer, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Chad", ",", "are", "we", "heading", "towards", "a", "particularly", "extreme", "summer", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "We're heading to a particularly extreme hurricane season, according to the Hurricane Center, 13 to 20 named storms, almost double possibly the number of hurricanes, and double possibly the number of major hurricanes.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "heading", "to", "a", "particularly", "extreme", "hurricane", "season", ",", "according", "to", "the", "Hurricane", "Center", ",", "13", "to", "20", "named", "storms", ",", "almost", "double", "possibly", "the", "number", "of", "hurricanes", ",", "and", "double", "possibly", "the", "number", "of", "major", "hurricanes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Are the FBI in the belief that it's all the same person?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "the", "FBI", "in", "the", "belief", "that", "it", "'s", "all", "the", "same", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Well, there are two separate cases, actually, both involving ricin letters.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "are", "two", "separate", "cases", ",", "actually", ",", "both", "involving", "ricin", "letters", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "CC", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "What do you make of this latest ricin letter attack on the president and on Mayor Bloomberg?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "this", "latest", "ricin", "letter", "attack", "on", "the", "president", "and", "on", "Mayor", "Bloomberg", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "Well, it's intended I think to attract publicity which it certainly is, intended to potentially intimidate but quite clearly the president and the mayor are not going to be intimidated by it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "intended", "I", "think", "to", "attract", "publicity", "which", "it", "certainly", "is", ",", "intended", "to", "potentially", "intimidate", "but", "quite", "clearly", "the", "president", "and", "the", "mayor", "are", "not", "going", "to", "be", "intimidated", "by", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mayor Bloomberg"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "How worried would you be if you were running the FBI or an organization like that now or even a city police force, how worrying is it that it's so easy now to make guns, bombs, poison?", "question_tokens": ["How", "worried", "would", "you", "be", "if", "you", "were", "running", "the", "FBI", "or", "an", "organization", "like", "that", "now", "or", "even", "a", "city", "police", "force", ",", "how", "worrying", "is", "it", "that", "it", "'s", "so", "easy", "now", "to", "make", "guns", ",", "bombs", ",", "poison", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBG", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Well, that is the concern.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "is", "the", "concern", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "What can you do about such blatant, emblazon incitement to violence in a publication?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "do", "about", "such", "blatant", ",", "emblazon", "incitement", "to", "violence", "in", "a", "publication", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "NN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Really nothing.", "answer_tokens": ["Really", "nothing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI", "Massachusetts State Police"]}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Would you think this needs a police investigation?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "think", "this", "needs", "a", "police", "investigation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "It's having a very comprehensive investigation conducted by both the FBI and the Massachusetts State Police that there's an old adage in policing, the first story is never the correct story.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "having", "a", "very", "comprehensive", "investigation", "conducted", "by", "both", "the", "FBI", "and", "the", "Massachusetts", "State", "Police", "that", "there", "'s", "an", "old", "adage", "in", "policing", ",", "the", "first", "story", "is", "never", "the", "correct", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Donnie, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Donnie", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Hey, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["New Yorkers"], "LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "``", "JJ", "NNS", "''", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "Where were you when you heard about the Boston marathon bombings and what was your first reaction?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "when", "you", "heard", "about", "the", "Boston", "marathon", "bombings", "and", "what", "was", "your", "first", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "I was on set on my TV series \"Blue Bloods\" in New York and was surrounded by New Yorkers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "on", "set", "on", "my", "TV", "series", "``", "Blue", "Bloods", "''", "in", "New", "York", "and", "was", "surrounded", "by", "New", "Yorkers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Boston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "And Donnie, when you discovered that the perpetrators of this atrocity were two young brothers who had been living in Boston for quite a long time and had suddenly committed this outrage, what was your view of that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Donnie", ",", "when", "you", "discovered", "that", "the", "perpetrators", "of", "this", "atrocity", "were", "two", "young", "brothers", "who", "had", "been", "living", "in", "Boston", "for", "quite", "a", "long", "time", "and", "had", "suddenly", "committed", "this", "outrage", ",", "what", "was", "your", "view", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Well, it's frightening.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "frightening", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donnie"], "LOCATION": ["Boston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "How do you feel about being able to put on such an amazing show in your own city for your own people?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "being", "able", "to", "put", "on", "such", "an", "amazing", "show", "in", "your", "own", "city", "for", "your", "own", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "It's a wonderful feeling, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "wonderful", "feeling", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "CC", "TO", "NN", "CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "What do you say to them to try and make their lives a little better?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "them", "to", "try", "and", "make", "their", "lives", "a", "little", "better", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "Well, there's nothing -- there's no real way to adequately respond or to minister or -- you know, I don't even think we can really understand entirely what's happened.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "nothing", "--", "there", "'s", "no", "real", "way", "to", "adequately", "respond", "or", "to", "minister", "or", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "even", "think", "we", "can", "really", "understand", "entirely", "what", "'s", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "RBS", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "What do you think from all you've gleaned about the way the money should be spent is going to be the most effective way of using this large amount of cash?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "from", "all", "you", "'ve", "gleaned", "about", "the", "way", "the", "money", "should", "be", "spent", "is", "going", "to", "be", "the", "most", "effective", "way", "of", "using", "this", "large", "amount", "of", "cash", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "I hope the people in charge of the concert who have been in direct contact with the families will have a sense of what -- how they need it the most and what's the most effective way to distribute it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "the", "people", "in", "charge", "of", "the", "concert", "who", "have", "been", "in", "direct", "contact", "with", "the", "families", "will", "have", "a", "sense", "of", "what", "--", "how", "they", "need", "it", "the", "most", "and", "what", "'s", "the", "most", "effective", "way", "to", "distribute", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "And James, finally for you, what does it mean to you to be a Bostonian?", "question_tokens": ["And", "James", ",", "finally", "for", "you", ",", "what", "does", "it", "mean", "to", "you", "to", "be", "a", "Bostonian", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "Well, I was born here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "born", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brian Panitch", "Katherine Jackson", "Michael", "Katherine", "Mr. Gongaware", "Mr. Gongaware"]}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "WP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "What was going on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Well, my understanding is that Brian Panitch, the lawyer for Katherine Jackson and Michael's children, who incidentally I recommended to Katherine as the best lawyer in the country to handle this case, he's been going over e-mails with Mr. Gongaware and I'm told that Mr. Gongaware is professing not to remember exactly why he did the mail or what he meant, answering very often I don't recall, I don't recall, I don't recall.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "understanding", "is", "that", "Brian", "Panitch", ",", "the", "lawyer", "for", "Katherine", "Jackson", "and", "Michael", "'s", "children", ",", "who", "incidentally", "I", "recommended", "to", "Katherine", "as", "the", "best", "lawyer", "in", "the", "country", "to", "handle", "this", "case", ",", "he", "'s", "been", "going", "over", "e-mails", "with", "Mr.", "Gongaware", "and", "I", "'m", "told", "that", "Mr.", "Gongaware", "is", "professing", "not", "to", "remember", "exactly", "why", "he", "did", "the", "mail", "or", "what", "he", "meant", ",", "answering", "very", "often", "I", "do", "n't", "recall", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "recall", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "recall", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Is it any defense to say you don't recall sending an e-mail when there's a copy of the e-mail sitting in court?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "any", "defense", "to", "say", "you", "do", "n't", "recall", "sending", "an", "e-mail", "when", "there", "'s", "a", "copy", "of", "the", "e-mail", "sitting", "in", "court", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Well, it's a problem, Piers, because when a witness continues to say, says over and over, I don't recall, as apparently this witness has, then it starts to give the impression of untruthfulness to the jury and, in fact, it's reported that the jury began to laugh when this witness continued to say, I don't recall, and when the jury begins to laugh at the witness, it should be a cause for concern by the defense that perhaps the jury's thinking this witness is just not credible.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "problem", ",", "Piers", ",", "because", "when", "a", "witness", "continues", "to", "say", ",", "says", "over", "and", "over", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "recall", ",", "as", "apparently", "this", "witness", "has", ",", "then", "it", "starts", "to", "give", "the", "impression", "of", "untruthfulness", "to", "the", "jury", "and", ",", "in", "fact", ",", "it", "'s", "reported", "that", "the", "jury", "began", "to", "laugh", "when", "this", "witness", "continued", "to", "say", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "recall", ",", "and", "when", "the", "jury", "begins", "to", "laugh", "at", "the", "witness", ",", "it", "should", "be", "a", "cause", "for", "concern", "by", "the", "defense", "that", "perhaps", "the", "jury", "'s", "thinking", "this", "witness", "is", "just", "not", "credible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Tom, what do you make of this case?", "question_tokens": ["Tom", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "this", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Well, I think it's a tragedy for this family and I think the heat is going to be so intense on the Mexican government that she'll be released at some point.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "tragedy", "for", "this", "family", "and", "I", "think", "the", "heat", "is", "going", "to", "be", "so", "intense", "on", "the", "Mexican", "government", "that", "she", "'ll", "be", "released", "at", "some", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "If this was your client, though, what would you be doing now to try and put the maximum type of pressure on to the Mexican authorities to get her out of there?", "question_tokens": ["If", "this", "was", "your", "client", ",", "though", ",", "what", "would", "you", "be", "doing", "now", "to", "try", "and", "put", "the", "maximum", "type", "of", "pressure", "on", "to", "the", "Mexican", "authorities", "to", "get", "her", "out", "of", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "RP", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Well, I would do just exactly what was done today and CNN in fact have seen what I'm going to call the smoking video.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "do", "just", "exactly", "what", "was", "done", "today", "and", "CNN", "in", "fact", "have", "seen", "what", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "call", "the", "smoking", "video", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Did you ever think you'd have to deal with three scandals like this at the same time?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "think", "you", "'d", "have", "to", "deal", "with", "three", "scandals", "like", "this", "at", "the", "same", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "I dismiss the premise, the idea that these were scandals.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "dismiss", "the", "premise", ",", "the", "idea", "that", "these", "were", "scandals", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "The obvious question, Margaret Hoover, are they scandals?", "question_tokens": ["The", "obvious", "question", ",", "Margaret", "Hoover", ",", "are", "they", "scandals", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Margaret Hoover"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "How scandalized can they be if that's what they want him to do?", "question_tokens": ["How", "scandalized", "can", "they", "be", "if", "that", "'s", "what", "they", "want", "him", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Why is he getting more popular through this period rather than less?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "he", "getting", "more", "popular", "through", "this", "period", "rather", "than", "less", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Because the American people know that even if there are scandals, they're not presidential scandals, they have nothing to do with him.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "the", "American", "people", "know", "that", "even", "if", "there", "are", "scandals", ",", "they", "'re", "not", "presidential", "scandals", ",", "they", "have", "nothing", "to", "do", "with", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Should Eric Holder resign?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "Eric", "Holder", "resign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "I think you need an independent -- I think you need an independent people --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "need", "an", "independent", "--", "I", "think", "you", "need", "an", "independent", "people", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 473, "question": "A God-given right?", "question_tokens": ["A", "God-given", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "It is a --", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "a", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "How about a constitutional right?", "question_tokens": ["How", "about", "a", "constitutional", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Well, and -- yes, it is a constitutional right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "and", "--", "yes", ",", "it", "is", "a", "constitutional", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Is it a God-given right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "a", "God-given", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "You know, here's the deal, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "here", "'s", "the", "deal", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Yes or no?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "or", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "This -- no, it is not a God-given right.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "--", "no", ",", "it", "is", "not", "a", "God-given", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Is it surprising that you're getting some people now flipping and doing this kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "surprising", "that", "you", "'re", "getting", "some", "people", "now", "flipping", "and", "doing", "this", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "You've always --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "always", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "I was curious about his link -- you know, some -- not just constitutional right but a God-given right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "was", "curious", "about", "his", "link", "--", "you", "know", ",", "some", "--", "not", "just", "constitutional", "right", "but", "a", "God-given", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ":", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "ILL: Well, there are a lot of people who believe that these are natural rights and these inalienable constitutional rights are given to us because we are endowed them by our Creator.", "answer_tokens": ["ILL", ":", "Well", ",", "there", "are", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "who", "believe", "that", "these", "are", "natural", "rights", "and", "these", "inalienable", "constitutional", "rights", "are", "given", "to", "us", "because", "we", "are", "endowed", "them", "by", "our", "Creator", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 542, "question": "Is he a nut, though, being driven, whoever this person is, by nutty rhetoric from extremists?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "a", "nut", ",", "though", ",", "being", "driven", ",", "whoever", "this", "person", "is", ",", "by", "nutty", "rhetoric", "from", "extremists", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Do you think it's one of those things that in the end it will change?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "one", "of", "those", "things", "that", "in", "the", "end", "it", "will", "change", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "I think it could, but the difference between that and say civil rights or that and these other issues is big money.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "could", ",", "but", "the", "difference", "between", "that", "and", "say", "civil", "rights", "or", "that", "and", "these", "other", "issues", "is", "big", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "Good thing we have to be with you, right?", "question_tokens": ["Good", "thing", "we", "have", "to", "be", "with", "you", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "That's actually what it is.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "actually", "what", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]